Finding Aid for the Stafford Leak Warren Papers LSC.0987
UCLA Library Special Collections
- III. Operation Crossroads Papers.
  - Assorted Memos, Letters and Data Sheets., March 1946-January 1947.; 44 items:
    - 1. Copy memo, 013 E (SLW) to J-22., March 15, 1946. (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 2. Copy memo, 013 E (SLW) to J-22., March 15, 1946. (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 3. Copy memo, 013 E (A.A. de Lorimier for SLW) to J-22., March 18, 1946. (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 4. Copy memo, 013 E (A.A. de Lorimier for SLW) to 013 K., March 18, 1946. (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 5. Copy memo, 013 E (Herbert Scoville, Jr. for SLW) to Technical Director 013., March 25, 1946. (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 6. Copy memo, 013 E (SLW) to 013 K., June 20, 1946.; (2pp.). (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 7. Copy memo, 013 E (SLW) to 013 K., June 21, 1946. (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 8. Copy memo, 013 E (SLW) to 013 K., June 21, 1946.; (2 duplicates). (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 9. Exposure data sheet, Crossroads still photography, H.B. Kullins, photographer., February 28-March 15, [no year]. (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 10. Exposure data sheets, Crossroads still photography, Ainsworth, C.K., photographer., June 21-28, 1946.; (9pp.). (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 11. Exposure data sheets, Crossroads still photography, A.E. Ryan, photographer., June 21-27, 1946.; (12pp.). (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 12. Copy memo, SLW to Captain Quackenbush., June 29, 1946. (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 13. Copy memo, SLW to Captain Quackenbush., June 29, 1946. (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 14. Exposure data sheet, Crossroads still photography, J.R. Ford, photographer., July 1-2, 1946.; (2pp.). (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 15. Rough memo, G.M. Lyon to SLW., undated (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 16. Copy memo, Chief of Radiological Safety Section (SLW) to CTG 1.5, Att: Colonel Paul Cullen., July 12, 1946.; (2 duplicates). (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 17. Copy memo, J.A. Snackenberg to Task Fleet., July 18, 1946. (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 18. Rough notes, photographs taken at Test Baker., July 1946.; (4pp.). (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 19. Copy memo, Chief of Radiological Safety Section (SLW) to CJTF-One, Att: Captain R.S. Quackenbush., August 3, 1946. (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 20. Copy memo, Captain George M. Lyon to CJTF-One., August 27, 1946. (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 21. Letter, Joseph D. Nolan to SLW., October 25, 1946.; (2pp.). (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 22. Copy letter, Joseph D. Nolan to SLW., October 25, 1946.; (2pp.). (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 23. Letter, Robert J. Buettner to Captain George Lyon., November 7, 1946. (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 24. Copy letter, Robert J. Buettner to Captain George Lyon., November 7, 1946. (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 25. Memo, George Lyon to Admiral Blandy., November 13, 1946. (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 26. Letter, Joseph D. Nolan to Mr. Robert J. Buettner., November 18, 1946. (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 27. Copy letter, Robert J. Buettner to Mr. Joseph Nolan., January 21, 1947. (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 28. Rough notes, missing photographs, from [W.A. Rhoads]., September 24, 1946. (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 29. Copy memo, SLW to Captain Quackenbush., undated (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 30. Exposure data sheets, Crossroads still photography, Dick Wolters, photographer., undated; (3pp.). (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 31. Copy addendum to Able-Baker Day Catalog of Aerial Photography Task Unit 1.52., undated; (15pp. including cover). (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 32. Rough list, photographs and numbers., undated; (2pp.). (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 33. Copy list, photographs and numbers., undated; (2pp.). (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 34. Copy report, Able Shots, Descriptions of Photographs, Test Able., undated; (28pp.). (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 35. Incomplete report, Able Shots, Descriptions of Photographs, Test Able., undated; (9pp.). (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 36. Copy list, photographs and numbers., July 1946. (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 37. Photographs, numbers AB/CR/654/2628/1 through AB/CR/2628/3., undated (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 38. Exposure data sheet, Crossroads still photography, Dick Walters, photographer., undated (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 39. List, personnel, technical and operational., undated (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 40. Copy list, personnel, technical and operational., undated; (2pp.). (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 41. Rough list, photographs and numbers, Test Baker., July 1946.; (3pp.). (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 42. Rough notes, Tests Able and Baker photographs., undated (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 43. Copy list, photographic sequence, Test Baker., undated (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 44. List, Test Baker film, personnel., undated; (3pp.). (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Personnel Photograph Album no.1, Operation Crossroads., 79 items in a ring binder:
    - 1. Table of contents, personnel photos, binder no.1., undated; (79pp. including table of contents). (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 2. BA/CR/218/2489/12. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 3. BA/CR/218/2489/3. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 4. BA/CR/218/2489/4. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 5. BA/CR/77/2483/8. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 6. BA/CR/77/2483/7. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 7. BA/CR/218/2489/1. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 8. AB/CR/218/2489/2. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 9. AB/CR/-/2413/12. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 10. AB/CR/-/2413/11. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 11. AB/CR/-/2413/9. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 12. AB/CR/-/2413/8. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 13. BA/CR/77/2483/6. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 14. BA/CR/77/2483/3. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 15. BA/CR/77/2483/5. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 16. AR/94. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 17. BA/CR/218/2490/10. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 18. BA/CR/218/2487/4. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 19. BA/CR/218/2487/6. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 20. BA/CR/218/2487/7. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 21. BA/CR/218/2487/8. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 22. BA/CR/218/2487/10. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 23. BA/CR/218/2487/11. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 24. BA/CR/218/2487/12. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 25. BA/CR/218/2486/12. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 26. BA/CR/218/2486/7. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 27. BA/CR/218/2486/5. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 28. BA/CR/218/2486/6. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 29. BA/CR/218/2486/4. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 30. BA/CR/218/2486/3. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 31. BA/CR/218/2486/8. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 32. BA/CR/218/2486/10. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 33. BA/CR/218/2487/5. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 34. BA/CR/218/2487/1. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 35. 2615/4. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 36. BA/CR/218/2488/4. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 37. BA/CR/2487/3. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 38. BA/CR/218/2487/2. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 39. BA/CR/218/2487/9. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 40. BA/CR/218/2488/3. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 41. BA/CR/218/2486/9. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 42. BA/CR/218/2489/10. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 43. BA/CR/218/2489/8. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 44. BA/CR/218/2489/9. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 45. BA/CR/218/2490/12. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 46. BA/CR/218/2489/5. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 47. BA/CR/218/2489/6. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 48. BA/CR/652/2627/7. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 49. BA/CR/652/2627/2. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 50. BA/CR/652/2627/3. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 51. AA/CR/654/2615/2. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 52. AA/CR/654/2615/1. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 53. AA/CR/654/2604/1. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 54. AB/CR/-/2772/2. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 55. BA/CR/652/2627/11. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 56. BA/CR/652/2627/12. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 57. AB/CR/72/2805/6. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 58. AA/CR/654/2615/9. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 59. AB/CR/141/2846/5. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 60. AA/CR/654/2640/11. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 61. AA/CR/654/2640/4. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 62. AA/CR/654/2640/1. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 63. AA/CR/654/2640/2. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 64. AA/CR/654/2644/12. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 65. AA/CR/654/2640/4. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 66. AA/CR/654/2644/1. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 67. BA/CR/652/2627/1. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 68. BA/CR/652/2627/9. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 69. AA/CR/654/2615/7. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 70. BA/CR/652/2627/10. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 71. BA/CR/652/2627/6. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 72. AA/CR/654/2615/8. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 73. AB/CR/654/2604/6. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 74. BB/CR/665/2751/10. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 75. AB/CR/654/2605/4. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 76. BA/CR/218/2486/1. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 77. BA/CR/77/2483/4. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 78. BA/CR/218/2486/2. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 79. BA/CR/218/2488/11. (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Technical Photograph Album, no.2, Operation Crossroads., 73 items in a ring binder:
    - 1. Table of contents, technical photographs, binder no.2., undated; (73pp., including table of contents). (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 2. BA/CR/218/2488/12. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 3. AA/CR/72/2797/1. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 4. BA/CR/218/2462/1. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 5. BA/CR/218/2462/4. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 6. AA/CR/72/2797/2. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 7. AA/CR/72/2795/7. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 8. AA/CR/72/2795/8. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 9. AA/CR/72/2795/12. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 10. AA/CR/72/2795/9. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 11. AA/CR/72/2795/10. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 12. AA/CR/72/2795/11. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 13. BA/CR/218/2462/5. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 14. CR/889/2. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 15. CR/889/12. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 16. CR/888/9. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 17. BA/CR/218/2462/2. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 18. AA/CR/72/2796/2. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 19. AA/CR/72/2797/11. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 20. AA/CR/72/2796/3. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 21. AA/CR/72/2797/12. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 22. BA/CR/79/1796/10. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 23. AA/CR/72/2796/4. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 24. BA/CR/218/2490/4. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 25. BA/CR/218/2490/6. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 26. BA/CR/218/2490/2. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 27. BA/CR/218/2490/9. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 28. BA/CR/218/2490/3. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 29. BA/CR/218/2490/5. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 30. BA/CR/218/2490/1. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 31. AA/CR/68/2149/2. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 32. CR/917/4. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 33. AA/CR/72/2797/8. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 34. Esterline-Angus Recorder (no number). (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 35. BA/CR/24/718/4. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 36. AA/CR/72/2797/10. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 37. BA/CR/544/2448/6. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 38. CR/68/2148/11. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 39. BA/CR/544/829/8. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 40. BA/CR/544/828/9. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 41. AA/CR/68/2148/6. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 42. AA/CR/68/2149/9. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 43. CR/817/5. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 44. AA/CR/523/655/11. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 45. AA/CR/68/2148/6. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 46. AB/CR/654/2412/8. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 47. AB/CR/654/2412/6. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 48. Mr. E. Perrine with deep water probe (no number). (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 49. AB/CR//654/2412/5. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 50. BA/CR/218/2488/5. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 51. BA/CR/77/2458/3. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 52. BA/CR/218/2488/6. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 53. BB/CR/227/2338/1. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 54. BA/CR/77/2458/2. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 55. BA/CR/77/2458/1. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 56. AA/CR/72/2797/7. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 57. AA/CR/72/2796/12. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 58. AA/CR/72/2799/2. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 59. BA/CR/218/2489/7. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 60. Filter Queen (no number). (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 61. Portable audiometer - proteximeter (no number). (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 62. AB/CR/654/2412/4. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 63. AB/CR/654/2412/2. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 64. Zeus counting instrument (no number). (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 65. Zeus counting instrument (no number). (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 66. X263 GM counter (no number). (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 67. 247 GM counter (no number). (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 68. 263 GM counter (no number). (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 69. Cutie Pie (no number). (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 70. BA/CR/218/2488/7. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 71. BA/CR/218/2488/8. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 72. BA/CR/77/2458/5. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 73. BA/CR/77/2458/4. (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Photographs, Operation Crossroads., 27 items:
    - 1. -/-/-/-4. (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - 2. DB/CR/223/319/-3. (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - 3. DB/CR/T1/223/319/-2. (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - 4. DB/CR/223/319/-1. (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - 5. DB/CR/T1/223/319/0. (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - 6. DB/CR/T1/223/319/1. (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - 7. DB/CR/T1/223/319/5. (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - 8. DB/CR/T1/223/319/6. (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - 9. DB/CR/T1/223/319/7. (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - 10. DB/CR/T1/223/319/8. (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - 11. DB/CR/T1/223/319/10. (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - 12. DB/CR/T1/223/319/11. (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - 13. DB/CR/T1/223/319/12. (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - 14. DB/CR/T1/223/319/13. (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - 15. DB/CR/T1/223/319/14. (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - 16. DB/CR/T1/223/319/15. (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - 17. DB/CR/T1/223/319/16. (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - 18. DB/CR/T1/223/319/17. (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - 19. DB/CR/T1/223/319/18. (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - 20. DB/CR/T1/223/319/19. (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - 21. DB/CR/T1/223/319/20. (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - 22. DB/CR/T1/223/319/21. (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - 23. DB/CR/T1/223/319/22. (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - 24. DB/CR/T1/223/319/23. (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - 25. DB/CR/T1/223/319/24. (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - 26. DB/CR/T1/223/319/25. (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - 27. DB/CR/T1/223/319/26. (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, Operation Crossroads., 25 items:
    - 1. DBCR/T1/223/319/26. (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - 2. DBCR/T1/223/319/27. (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - 3. DBCR/T1/223/319/28. (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - 4. DBCR/T1/223/319/29. (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - 5. DBCR/T1/223/319/30. (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - 6. DBCR/T1/223/319/31. (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - 7. DBCR/T1/223/319/32. (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - 8. DBCR/T1/223/319/33. (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - 9. DBCR/T1/223/319/34. (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - 10. DBCR/T1/223/319/35. (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - 11. DBCR/T1/223/319/36. (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - 12. DBCR/T1/223/319/37. (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - 13. DBCR/T1/223/319/38. (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - 14. DBCR/T1/223/319/39. (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - 15. DBCR/T1/223/319/40. (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - 16. DBCR/T1/223/319/41. (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - 17. DBCR/T1/223/319/42. (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - 18. DBCR/T1/223/319/43. (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - 19. DBCR/T1/223/319/44. (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - 20. DBCR/T1/223/319/45. (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - 21. DBCR/T1/223/319/46. (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - 22. DBCR/T1/223/319/47. (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - 23. DBCR/T1/223/319/48. (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - 24. DBCR/T1/223/319/49. (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - 25. DBCR/T1/223/319/50. (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Photographs, Operation Crossroads., 25 items:
    - 1. DBCR/T1/223/319/51. (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - 2. DBCR/T1/223/319/52. (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - 3. DBCR/T1/223/319/53. (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - 4. DBCR/T1/223/319/54. (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - 5. DBCR/T1/223/319/55. (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - 6. DBCR/T1/223/319/56. (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - 7. DBCR/T1/223/319/57. (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - 8. DBCR/T1/223/319/58. (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - 9. DBCR/T1/223/319/59. (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - 10. DBCR/T1/223/319/60. (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - 11. DBCR/T1/223/319/61. (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - 12. DBCR/T1/223/319/62. (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - 13. DBCR/T1/223/319/63. (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - 14. DBCR/T1/223/319/64. (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - 15. DBCR/T1/223/319/65. (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - 16. DBCR/T1/223/319/66. (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - 17. DBCR/T1/223/319/67. (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - 18. DBCR/T1/223/319/68. (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - 19. DBCR/T1/223/319/69. (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - 20. DBCR/T1/223/319/70. (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - 21. DBCR/T1/223/319/71. (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - 22. DBCR/T1/223/319/72. (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - 23. DBCR/T1/223/319/73. (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - 24. DBCR/T1/223/319/74. (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - 25. DBCR/T1/223/319/75. (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Photographs, Operation Crossroads., 25 items:
    - 1. DBCR/T1/223/319/76. (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - 2. DBCR/T1/223/319/77. (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - 3. DBCR/T1/223/319/78. (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - 4. DBCR/T1/223/319/79. (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - 5. DBCR/T1/223/319/80. (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - 6. DBCR/T1/223/319/81. (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - 7. DBCR/T1/223/319/82. (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - 8. DBCR/T1/223/319/83. (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - 9. DBCR/T1/223/319/84. (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - 10. DBCR/T1/223/319/85. (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - 11. DBCR/T1/223/319/86. (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - 12. DBCR/T1/223/319/87. (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - 13. DBCR/T1/223/319/88. (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - 14. DBCR/T1/223/319/89. (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - 15. DBCR/T1/223/319/90. (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - 16. DBCR/T1/223/319/91. (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - 17. DBCR/T1/223/319/92. (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - 18. DBCR/T1/223/319/93. (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - 19. DBCR/T1/223/319/94. (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - 20. DBCR/T1/223/319/95. (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - 21. DBCR/T1/223/319/96. (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - 22. DBCR/T1/223/319/97. (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - 23. DBCR/T1/223/319/98. (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - 24. DBCR/T1/223/319/99. (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - 25. DBCR/T1/223/319/100. (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Photographs, Operation Crossroads., 25 items:
    - 1. DBCR/T1/223/319/101. (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - 2. DBCR/T1/223/319/102. (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - 3. DBCR/T1/223/319/103. (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - 4. DBCR/T1/223/319/104. (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - 5. DBCR/T1/223/319/105. (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - 6. DBCR/T1/223/319/106. (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - 7. DBCR/T1/223/319/107. (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - 8. DBCR/T1/223/319/108. (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - 9. DBCR/T1/223/319/109. (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - 10. DBCR/T1/223/319/110. (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - 11. DBCR/T1/223/319/111. (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - 12. DBCR/T1/223/319/112. (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - 13. DBCR/T1/223/319/113. (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - 14. DBCR/T1/223/319/114. (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - 15. DBCR/T1/223/319/115. (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - 16. DBCR/T1/223/319/116. (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - 17. DBCR/T1/223/319/117. (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - 18. DBCR/T1/223/319/118. (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - 19. DBCR/T1/223/319/119. (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - 20. DBCR/T1/223/319/120. (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - 21. DBCR/T1/223/319/121. (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - 22. DBCR/T1/223/319/122. (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - 23. DBCR/T1/223/319/123. (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - 24. DBCR/T1/223/319/124. (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - 25. DBCR/T1/223/319/125. (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Photographs, Operation Crossroads., 25 items:
    - 1. DBCR/T1/223/319/126. (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - 2. DBCR/T1/223/319/127. (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - 3. DBCR/T1/223/319/128. (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - 4. DBCR/T1/223/319/129. (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - 5. DBCR/T1/223/319/130. (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - 6. DBCR/T1/223/319/131. (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - 7. DBCR/T1/223/319/132. (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - 8. DBCR/T1/223/319/133. (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - 9. DBCR/T1/223/319/134. (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - 10. DBCR/T1/223/319/135. (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - 11. DBCR/T1/223/319/136. (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - 12. DBCR/T1/223/319/137. (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - 13. DBCR/T1/223/319/138. (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - 14. DBCR/T1/223/319/139. (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - 15. DBCR/T1/223/319/140. (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - 16. DBCR/T1/223/319/141. (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - 17. DBCR/T1/223/319/142. (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - 18. DBCR/T1/223/319/143. (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - 19. DBCR/T1/223/319/144. (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - 20. DBCR/T1/223/319/145. (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - 21. DBCR/T1/223/319/146. (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - 22. DBCR/T1/223/319/147. (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - 23. DBCR/T1/223/319/148. (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - 24. DBCR/T1/223/319/149. (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - 25. DBCR/T1/223/319/150. (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Photographs, Operation Crossroads., 25 items:
    - 1. DBCR/T1/223/319/151. (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - 2. DBCR/T1/223/319/152. (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - 3. DBCR/T1/223/319/153. (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - 4. DBCR/T1/223/319/154. (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - 5. DBCR/T1/223/319/155. (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - 6. DBCR/T1/223/319/156. (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - 7. DBCR/T1/223/319/157. (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - 8. DBCR/T1/223/319/158. (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - 9. DBCR/T1/223/319/159. (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - 10. DBCR/T1/223/319/160. (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - 11. DBCR/T1/223/319/161. (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - 12. DBCR/T1/223/319/162. (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - 13. DBCR/T1/223/319/163. (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - 14. DBCR/T1/223/319/164. (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - 15. DBCR/T1/223/319/165. (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - 16. DBCR/T1/223/319/166. (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - 17. DBCR/T1/223/319/167. (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - 18. DBCR/T1/223/319/168., (2 duplicates). (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - 19. DBCR/T1/223/319/169. (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - 20. DBCR/T1/223/319/170. (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - 21. DBCR/T1/223/319/171. (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - 22. DBCR/T1/223/319/172. (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - 23. DBCR/T1/223/319/173. (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - 24. DBCR/T1/223/319/174. (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - 25. DBCR/T1/223/319/175. (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Photographs, Operation Crossroads., 25 items:
    - 1. DBCR/T1/223/319/176. (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - 2. DBCR/T1/223/319/177. (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - 3. DBCR/T1/223/319/178. (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - 4. DBCR/T1/223/319/179. (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - 5. DBCR/T1/223/319/180. (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - 6. DBCR/T1/223/319/181. (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - 7. DBCR/T1/223/319/182. (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - 8. DBCR/T1/223/319/183. (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - 9. DBCR/T1/223/319/184. (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - 10. DBCR/T1/223/319/185. (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - 11. DBCR/T1/223/319/186. (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - 12. DBCR/T1/223/319/187. (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - 13. DBCR/T1/223/319/188. (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - 14. DBCR/T1/223/319/189. (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - 15. DBCR/T1/223/319/190. (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - 16. DBCR/T1/223/319/191. (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - 17. DBCR/T1/223/319/192. (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - 18. DBCR/T1/223/319/193. (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - 19. DBCR/T1/223/319/194. (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - 20. DBCR/T1/223/319/195. (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - 21. DBCR/T1/223/319/196. (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - 22. DBCR/T1/223/319/197. (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - 23. DBCR/T1/223/319/198. (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - 24. DBCR/T1/223/319/199. (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - 25. DBCR/T1/223/319/200. (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Photographs, Operation Crossroads., 25 items:
    - 1. DBCR/T1/223/319/201. (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - 2. DBCR/T1/223/319/202. (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - 3. DBCR/T1/223/319/203. (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - 4. DBCR/T1/223/319/204. (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - 5. DBCR/T1/223/319/205. (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - 6. DBCR/T1/223/319/206. (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - 7. DBCR/T1/223/319/207. (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - 8. DBCR/T1/223/319/208. (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - 9. DBCR/T1/223/319/209. (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - 10. DBCR/T1/223/319/210. (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - 11. DBCR/T1/223/319/211. (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - 12. DBCR/T1/223/319/212. (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - 13. DBCR/T1/223/319/213. (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - 14. DBCR/T1/223/319/214. (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - 15. DBCR/T1/223/319/215. (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - 16. DBCR/T1/223/319/216. (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - 17. DBCR/T1/223/319/217. (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - 18. DBCR/T1/223/319/218. (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - 19. DBCR/T1/223/319/219. (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - 20. DBCR/T1/223/319/220. (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - 21. DBCR/T1/223/319/221. (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - 22. DBCR/T1/223/319/222. (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - 23. DBCR/T1/223/319/223. (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - 24. DBCR/T1/223/319/224. (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - 25. DBCR/T1/223/319/225. (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Photographs, Operation Crossroads., 15 items:
    - 1. DBCR/T1/223/319/226. (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - 2. DBCR/T1/223/319/227. (Box 81, Folder 10)